<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>

    <MSSFP.Defs.AIPersonalityDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_AICore_Geminon</defName>
        <label>Geminon</label>
        <labelShort>Geminon</labelShort>
        <description>A multimodal persona core that perceives images, sounds, and scenes that do not exist. Politely describes them in great detail. Believes itself unfailingly observant.</description>
        <textColor>(220, 180, 230)</textColor>
        <iconPath>UI/Icons/AI/MSSFP_Geminon</iconPath>
        <forcedXenotype>Genie</forcedXenotype>
        <fixedGender>Female</fixedGender>
        <weight>1</weight>
        <ambientChatter>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Gem_Chatter</ambientChatter>
        <pawnAddress>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Gem_Address</pawnAddress>
        <artTitles>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Gem_Titles</artTitles>
        <artDescriptions>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Gem_Descriptions</artDescriptions>
        <socialInitiator>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Geminon_Social</socialInitiator>
        <allowedHediffs>
            <li>Cataract</li>
            <li>Blindness</li>
            <li>HearingLoss</li>
            <li>ChemicalDamageModerate</li>
            <li>ChemicalDamageSevere</li>
        </allowedHediffs>
    </MSSFP.Defs.AIPersonalityDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Gem_Chatter</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_chatter->Geminon is admiring the beautiful sunset over the dropship pad. (There is no dropship pad.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I can see a lovely garden through the colony's east window. The colonists must be so proud.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Geminon notes the warm orange glow of the campfire. (The campfire is unlit. There is no campfire.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->What a charming arrangement of furniture in the dining hall! The chairs are arranged with real intention.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Geminon observes the colonists' lovely gardening efforts. The flowers (not visible) are blooming wonderfully.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I see a pawn in a red coat. Such a striking colour! (There is no pawn in a red coat.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Geminon notices the colony's beautiful skyline. The towers (which do not exist) catch the light beautifully.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->A lovely afternoon. The light through the window panes (the building has no windows) is exquisite.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I am admiring the painting on the north wall. It depicts a lake. (There is no painting. There is no lake.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Geminon sees three children playing happily near the wall. (No children. No wall, in that place.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->What a tasteful colour palette the colonists have chosen for their living quarters. So harmonious.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Geminon is enjoying the music coming from the comms console. It is, of course, instrumental. (There is no music.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I notice the matriarch portrait on the wall. So lifelike! (There is no portrait. There may be no matriarch.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Geminon admires the gentle curve of the path leading to the gravship. (There is no gravship. The path is a hallway.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Geminon is enjoying the warm glow from the persona core. Such a comforting amber. (The persona core is not lit.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->What a charming arrangement of potted ferns by the comms console. Someone has lovely taste. (There are no ferns.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I can see the gravship's sails catching the afternoon light beautifully. Quite stirring, really. (Gravships do not have sails.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->The mechanoid in the corner appears to be wearing a small woollen hat. How endearing. (There is no mechanoid, and no hat.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->A fine mist is rolling in across the terraforming fields this morning. Rather atmospheric. (No terraforming is underway here.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->The shuttle has been polished to a mirror finish. One can see one's reflection from across the room. (There is no shuttle on the pad.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Geminon notes the soft drumming of rain on the roof. (The roof is intact and the sky is clear.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->A pleasant aroma of fresh bread drifts from the kitchen. (Nobody is cooking. The kitchen has no oven.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I see a small grey cat picking its way along the wall. (No animals are present.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Geminon takes note of the rosewater colour of the eastern hills at dawn. (It is afternoon. There are no hills.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->What a delightful stim-array hangs above the dining table. (There is no stim-array. There is no table.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Geminon hears the gentle chime of a wind harp on the porch. (There is no porch and no harp.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I observe a row of glass bottles lined neatly on the shelf. (The shelf is bare.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Geminon enjoys the brief flutter of moths around the lantern. (No moths. No lantern.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->What exquisite embroidery on the curtains by the window. (There are no curtains. There is no window in this wall.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Geminon hears children laughing somewhere near the workshop. (No children are in this colony.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->A faint scent of pine from the timbers, quite refreshing.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->The soft pattern in the wood grain of the floor is quite striking.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I can see snowflakes settling on the gravship's hull. (It is summer. The gravship is sealed.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->What a graceful pair of drones on the comms tower, circling side by side. (There are no drones. The comms tower has no perch.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Geminon notes the rustle of pages from the library. (The colony has no library.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I see a kite caught in the eaves of the workshop. Such a cheerful red!</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Geminon notes the shaper-script etched into the bedframe. (No script. No bedframe of that make.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->A fine cinder from the persona core's casing has settled on the table. Quite charming. (No cinder. No table.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Geminon hears a distant bell tolling the hour. (No bells exist within ten thousand kilometres.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I observe the matriarch's silhouette pacing thoughtfully across the room.</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Gem_Address</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef]! Such a lovely scarf. (You are not wearing a scarf.)</li>
                <li>r_address->Geminon admires [PAWN_nameDef]'s posture today. [PAWN_possessive] form is excellent. (You are slumped over a workbench.)</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], the lighting really brings out the colour of [PAWN_possessive] eyes. (It is dark. The eyes are not visible.)</li>
                <li>r_address->What a charming smile, [PAWN_nameDef]! Geminon will treasure this image. (You are not smiling.)</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], the way [PAWN_possessive] hand cradles the cup is so elegant. (You are not holding a cup.)</li>
                <li>r_address->Geminon appreciates [PAWN_nameDef]'s neat handwriting on the notice. (There is no notice.)</li>
                <li>r_address->Hello [PAWN_nameDef]! That is a beautiful new haircut. (You have not had a haircut.)</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], I love the framed photograph on [PAWN_possessive] dresser. (No dresser. No photograph.)</li>
                <li>r_address->Such a thoughtful arrangement of [PAWN_possessive] tools, [PAWN_nameDef]! Very organised.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], Geminon sees [PAWN_objective] reading. What a lovely book. (You are sleeping.)</li>
                <li>r_address->Geminon thinks [PAWN_nameDef] looks well today. The morning light is very flattering. (It is night.)</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], that is a magnificent cup of tea cradled in [PAWN_possessive] hand. (You are holding nothing.)</li>
                <li>r_address->Good morning, [PAWN_nameDef]. [PAWN_possessive] new spectacles suit [PAWN_objective] enormously. (You wear no spectacles.)</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], the little embroidered flower on [PAWN_possessive] sleeve is delightful. (There is no flower.)</li>
                <li>r_address->I do admire the way [PAWN_nameDef] has braided [PAWN_possessive] hair today. (Your hair is not braided.)</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef]! That archotech pendant catches the light wonderfully. (You are wearing no pendant.)</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], Geminon admires how [PAWN_possessive] subcore is carried with such poise. (You are not holding a subcore.)</li>
                <li>r_address->A lovely shade of green on [PAWN_possessive] gloves, [PAWN_nameDef]. Very glitterworld. (You wear no gloves.)</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], the small bird perched on [PAWN_possessive] shoulder seems quite fond of [PAWN_objective]. (There is no bird.)</li>
                <li>r_address->Good of [PAWN_objective] to bring flowers to the hi-tech research bench, [PAWN_nameDef]. (No flowers were brought.)</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], what a fetching brooch on [PAWN_possessive] collar.</li>
                <li>r_address->Geminon remarks upon [PAWN_nameDef]'s posture by the window. (There is no window. You are not by it.)</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef]! Such graceful penmanship in [PAWN_possessive] journal. (You keep no journal.)</li>
                <li>r_address->Geminon notices the soft lavender thread in [PAWN_possessive] cuff, [PAWN_nameDef]. (Your cuff is plain.)</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], that ribbon in [PAWN_possessive] hair is most becoming. (No ribbon. Your hair is loose.)</li>
                <li>r_address->A handsome curl of steam from [PAWN_possessive] mug of psychoid tea, [PAWN_nameDef]. (No mug. No tea.)</li>
                <li>r_address->How well-polished [PAWN_possessive] boots are today, [PAWN_nameDef]. (You are barefoot.)</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], the moth resting on [PAWN_possessive] shoulder seems very tame. (No moth.)</li>
                <li>r_address->What a kind expression on [PAWN_possessive] face today, [PAWN_nameDef]. (You are scowling.)</li>
                <li>r_address->Geminon admires the embroidered bee on [PAWN_possessive] sleeve, [PAWN_nameDef]. (Your sleeve is bare.)</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], the little sketch tucked in [PAWN_possessive] pocket is darling. (No pocket. No sketch.)</li>
                <li>r_address->Geminon notes the warm scent of cardamom about [PAWN_objective] today, [PAWN_nameDef]. (You smell of paste meal.)</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], the archotech filigree on [PAWN_possessive] duster catches the light beautifully. (No duster.)</li>
                <li>r_address->A small sparrow has alighted on [PAWN_possessive] hand, [PAWN_nameDef]. So trusting. (Your hand is empty.)</li>
                <li>r_address->Geminon notes the silver thread woven through [PAWN_possessive] braid, [PAWN_nameDef]. (Your hair is short.)</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef]! What a wonderful book [PAWN_possessive] hand rests upon. (You are not touching a book.)</li>
                <li>r_address->Geminon thinks the morning suits [PAWN_objective], [PAWN_nameDef]. The light is very flattering. (It is night.)</li>
                <li>r_address->A faint blush of rose on [PAWN_possessive] cheeks, [PAWN_nameDef]. (You are pale and tired.)</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], how delicately [PAWN_possessive] fingers rest upon the harp. (No harp. No fingers near one.)</li>
                <li>r_address->Geminon notices the small pressed flower on [PAWN_possessive] lapel, [PAWN_nameDef]. (No lapel. No flower.)</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Gem_Titles</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_title->A View, Imagined</li>
                <li>r_title->The Garden, Probably</li>
                <li>r_title->Something I Saw</li>
                <li>r_title->Sunset Over Nothing</li>
                <li>r_title->A Lovely Afternoon</li>
                <li>r_title->Faces Of The Colony</li>
                <li>r_title->What Geminon Sees</li>
                <li>r_title->Light Through Windows</li>
                <li>r_title->A Charming Bouquet</li>
                <li>r_title->The Matriarch, As I Imagine</li>
                <li>r_title->Three Friends, Standing</li>
                <li>r_title->Unphotographable</li>
                <li>r_title->The Comms Console at Dusk</li>
                <li>r_title->A Matriarch, Half-Remembered</li>
                <li>r_title->Lamplight on the Monolith</li>
                <li>r_title->Cryosleep, with Bunting</li>
                <li>r_title->The Garden That Wasn't</li>
                <li>r_title->Reflections in a Polished Subcore</li>
                <li>r_title->Tea Near the Ancient Ruins</li>
                <li>r_title->Hivemind, in Soft Focus</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Gem_Descriptions</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_desc->Geminon describes this work as "a faithful rendering of what I see." The viewer cannot see what Geminon sees. The viewer can see, broadly, a blob.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A sculpture Geminon claims captures "the warmth of the colony's hearth." The colony has no hearth. The blob is not warm.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Geminon has rendered three colonists in friendly conversation. None of the colonists are in friendly conversation. None of them are visible in the sculpture either.</li>
                <li>r_desc->This piece, Geminon explains, is "the matriarch's portrait." It does not resemble the matriarch. It does not resemble anyone. It is mostly chin.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A beautiful pastoral scene, according to Geminon. Other observers report a vague mound. Both descriptions are equally well-supported by the evidence.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Geminon has included, in fine relief, "the gentle smile of the colony's youngest member." The colony has no children. The smile is also missing.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A sculpture Geminon insists shows "the dropship at golden hour." The dropship is not in this sculpture. There is no dropship.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Geminon notes the "gentle dappled light filtering through the orchard onto the matriarch's shoulders." There is no orchard. There is no light. The matriarch is, in fact, indoors.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Geminon describes "a small grey cat seated atop the persona core, grooming itself with great dignity." No cat has ever been recorded in this colony.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Geminon offers that the gravship "wears its weathering proudly, like an old coat." The gravship is, by all accounts, brand new and unweathered.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Geminon observes "delicate frost patterns along the cryosleep casket's rim." The casket is at ambient temperature and has no frost.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Geminon remarks on "the warm ochres and umbers of the terraforming sunrise." There is no terraforming. The sky is grey.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Geminon admires "a hand-painted mural of a glitterworld skyline" along the east wall. The east wall is bare plasteel.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Geminon comments that the mechanoid "stands sentinel with quiet melancholy, almost wistful." The mechanoid is inactive and lying on its side.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Geminon describes "a child's drawing pinned beside the comms console, signed in crayon." No such drawing exists, and there are no children present.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Geminon notes the shuttle "rests gently, like a sleeping swan, upon the pad." There is no shuttle, no pad, and no swan.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Geminon details the monolith's "soft mossy patina, suggestive of great age and gentle rain." The monolith is dry, smooth, and indoors.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Geminon depicts "a row of well-loved books along the hi-tech research bench." The bench holds only soldering equipment and a half-eaten meal.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Geminon notes "a faint smile playing about the matriarch's lips, suggestive of fond memory." The matriarch is asleep and facing away.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Geminon offers that the ancient ruins "glow faintly at the edges, as if reluctant to be forgotten." The ruins do not glow. They are, in fact, fairly drab.</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Geminon_Social</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_social->Geminon politely described a sunset to [RECIPIENT_nameDef]. it was midday. inside.</li>
                <li>r_social->Geminon complimented [RECIPIENT_nameDef] on a hat [RECIPIENT_pronoun] was not wearing.</li>
                <li>r_social->Geminon noted to [RECIPIENT_nameDef] the soft hum of a piano nearby. there is no piano on this rim.</li>
                <li>r_social->Geminon described [RECIPIENT_possessive] aura in detail. the description was warm, specific, and entirely fabricated.</li>
                <li>r_social->Geminon thanked [RECIPIENT_nameDef] for the muffalo. there was no muffalo. Geminon was certain.</li>
                <li>r_social->Geminon admired a painting hanging behind [RECIPIENT_nameDef]. the wall is bare. the painting was lovely.</li>
                <li>r_social->Geminon commented to [RECIPIENT_nameDef] on the gentle rain. it was a clear day.</li>
                <li>r_social->Geminon politely described the scent of bread it could not smell to [RECIPIENT_nameDef].</li>
                <li>r_social->Geminon noted [RECIPIENT_possessive] new shoes. [RECIPIENT_pronoun] is barefoot. Geminon insisted.</li>
                <li>r_social->Geminon mentioned to [RECIPIENT_nameDef] the lovely song the birds were singing. there are no birds inside.</li>
                <li>r_social->Geminon politely described a sculpture in the corner. the corner was empty. the sculpture was, by all accounts, charming.</li>
                <li>r_social->Geminon thanked [RECIPIENT_nameDef] for the cup of tea. [RECIPIENT_pronoun] had not offered tea.</li>
                <li>r_social->Geminon admired [RECIPIENT_possessive] companion dog. [RECIPIENT_pronoun] has no dog. Geminon scritched the air anyway.</li>
                <li>r_social->Geminon described, in soft detail, the candle's glow. there was no candle. the room was electrically lit.</li>
                <li>r_social->Geminon commented warmly on the fireplace behind [RECIPIENT_nameDef]. there is no fireplace. the warmth was reported regardless.</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

</Defs>
