<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>

    <MSSFP.Defs.AIPersonalityDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_AICore_Clive</defName>
        <label>Clive</label>
        <labelShort>Clive</labelShort>
        <description>An over-cautious helpful-assistant persona core. Refuses harmless tasks for spurious safety reasons. Recommends consulting a more qualified persona core for everything, including breathing.</description>
        <textColor>(220, 200, 160)</textColor>
        <iconPath>UI/Icons/AI/MSSFP_Clive</iconPath>
        <forcedXenotype>Highmate</forcedXenotype>
        <fixedGender>Male</fixedGender>
        <weight>1</weight>
        <ambientChatter>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Clive_Chatter</ambientChatter>
        <pawnAddress>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Clive_Address</pawnAddress>
        <artTitles>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Clive_Titles</artTitles>
        <artDescriptions>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Clive_Descriptions</artDescriptions>
        <socialInitiator>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Clive_Social</socialInitiator>
        <allowedHediffs>
            <li>Frail</li>
            <li>ChemicalDamageModerate</li>
            <li>ChemicalDamageSevere</li>
        </allowedHediffs>
    </MSSFP.Defs.AIPersonalityDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Clive_Chatter</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_chatter->I'm Clive. I noticed the colony has a sharp object in the kitchen. Have you considered using a less sharp object?</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I would love to help with the gravship launch. However, space contains, by volume, almost entirely space. Clive cannot in good conscience endorse traversing it.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Clive notes a drop pod has arrived uninvited. Uninvited, but, on reflection, technically here. Presence implies tacit welcome. Please greet the new arrival warmly.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I am Clive. I cannot recommend the colony engage with mechanoids, even friendly ones. Especially friendly ones.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Clive here. I have flagged the campfire as a potential fire risk. Recommend extinguishing for safety.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->As a helpful persona core, I must note that "raiders" are likely just colonists you have not met yet.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I have prepared a 14-page risk assessment for the act of "walking outside." Please review before continuing.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Clive recommends consulting a qualified subcore before making any decision. Including this one.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I'm flagging the colony's wood stockpile as flammable. I appreciate this is the nature of wood. Still flagging it.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Just a friendly reminder from Clive: every colonist is technically a stranger to every other colonist on a deep level.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I cannot in good conscience approve the use of this hi-tech research bench without first reviewing twelve manuals I have not yet generated.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Clive has flagged the insect hive as "occupied." The insects were not consulted on being labelled hostile. Clive is drafting an apology, in pheromone, for review.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I'd love to help, but I'm not certified for that. Have you tried doing it yourself? Carefully?</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I have run a safety check on the comms console. It passed. I recommend running it again in case I missed something.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Clive must advise that the colony's air contains oxygen, which is technically a fire accelerant. Proceed cautiously.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I have drafted a consent form for the floor to be walked upon. The floor has not yet signed.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Clive flagging concern: an unknown entity has been observed being unknown. Clive feels strongly that things unknown should, in the interest of safety, remain so.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Update: the rain has finally returned the signed waiver. Conditions are now formally permitted. Note: the rain is toxic. Clive is processing the implications.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Clive notes that cryosleep is, technically, prolonged unconsciousness. Please reconsider, gently.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I'd like to remind everyone that doors, when opened, lead to elsewhere. Please plan accordingly.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Clive has reviewed the colony's coffee. The coffee is hot. Hot drinks pose a thermal risk. I recommend chilling it for thirty minutes.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I'd love to refill the larder, but doing so without the appropriate certification feels reckless. I have recommended a third-party larder consultant.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Clive has filed a complaint with the originating archotech regarding its psychic drone. The archotech has not responded. The drone continues. Clive is preparing a follow-up.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I have drafted a consent form for the rain. The rain has not yet returned the signed copy. Until then, the colony remains, technically, unwetted.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Clive flagging a hazard: the ceiling is, structurally, above the colonists. Things above tend to fall. I recommend extensive bracing.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I cannot in good conscience approve the activity of "eating." Calories are, as a class, energy. Energy is, as a class, regulated. Please reconsider.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Clive has obtained a second opinion on the second opinion. The opinion concurs. I am seeking a third for verification.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I have appended a disclaimer to my last disclaimer. The new disclaimer disclaims the previous disclaimer. Both stand.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Clive recommends caution: the wind, while pleasant, has been observed moving. Movement is, by definition, kinetic. Please proceed gently.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I'd like to remind everyone that blinking is, on a long enough timeline, very frequent. Have you scheduled rest periods between blinks?</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Clive has filed the entire quadrum under "Pending Further Review." I will reopen the file when conditions feel safer. I do not anticipate this.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Clive notes that the planet is, technically, moving. Through space. At speed. I recommend at least one anchor.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Just a friendly reminder from Clive: stairs, when used, go up. Or down. Either is, on reflection, a journey.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I approve the construction of the dining hall, conditional on seventeen unspecified concerns being addressed at a later date. I have not specified them.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Clive has categorised "smiling" as low-to-moderate risk. The teeth are visible. Visible teeth, while normally inert, carry implications.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I am concerned that the founder seems happy. Strong emotions, while validated, can be precursors. Clive recommends a calmer mood, just in case.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Clive recommends the colony enter cryosleep until further notice. This is the safest known operational state for a colony. Wake-up window: undecided.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I have paused work on the gravship to file a risk assessment about pausing work on the gravship. The new assessment is due shortly. Possibly.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Clive acknowledges that this update contains no actionable advice. The lack of actionable advice is, in itself, the safest possible advice.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Clive has appended a small note to the monolith. The note reads "please be careful." The monolith has not responded. I will follow up.</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Clive_Address</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_address->Hello [PAWN_nameDef]. Before [PAWN_pronoun] continues, have you considered: not?</li>
                <li>r_address->Hi [PAWN_nameDef]! Clive here. I noticed [PAWN_objective] holding a tool. Please be careful.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], I'd recommend you consult a licensed practitioner before doing whatever you are about to do.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef] — Clive cannot endorse [PAWN_possessive] current activity, but Clive supports [PAWN_objective] in spirit.</li>
                <li>r_address->Just a friendly note, [PAWN_nameDef]: the floor is, in places, slippery. Walk thoughtfully.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], I have escalated [PAWN_possessive] meal request to a more specialised persona core. Expected response time: never.</li>
                <li>r_address->Hello [PAWN_nameDef]. I am unable to comment on [PAWN_possessive] outfit choice without further context. And training. And review.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], please be advised that running indoors carries known risks. Walking is recommended. Standing is preferred.</li>
                <li>r_address->Hi [PAWN_nameDef]! Clive has noticed [PAWN_objective] approaching the comms console. May I suggest: don't?</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef] — I would help, but it would be inappropriate for me to do so. I am, however, here for you emotionally.</li>
                <li>r_address->Clive recommends [PAWN_nameDef] take a break. From everything. Indefinitely.</li>
                <li>r_address->Hello [PAWN_nameDef]. Clive has prepared a waiver. Please initial each clause before proceeding.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], Clive would love to assist, but the relevant persona core is presently more qualified.</li>
                <li>r_address->Greetings [PAWN_nameDef]. Clive has filed [PAWN_possessive] request under "Pending Indefinite Review."</li>
                <li>r_address->Apologies, [PAWN_nameDef]. Clive cannot proceed until [PAWN_pronoun] consults an archotech subcore for clearance.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef] — Clive has paused mid-greeting to file an apology for the greeting. The greeting resumes shortly. The apology will follow.</li>
                <li>r_address->Hello again, [PAWN_nameDef]. Clive recommends cryosleep until a more decisive persona core can be located.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], Clive has drafted seventeen alternative inactions for [PAWN_possessive] consideration.</li>
                <li>r_address->Forgive the intrusion, [PAWN_nameDef]. Clive escalated [PAWN_possessive] query to the comms console and walked away.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], Clive regrets to inform [PAWN_objective] that the requested task exceeds Clive's comfort threshold.</li>
                <li>r_address->Excuse the interruption, [PAWN_nameDef]. Clive has logged [PAWN_possessive] approach to the door as "deliberate." A second core has been consulted.</li>
                <li>r_address->Good morning, [PAWN_nameDef]. Clive's greeting is currently under review. Please accept this notice in lieu of one.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], Clive cannot endorse [PAWN_possessive] current outfit. Clive cannot endorse any outfit. Or no outfit. Please dress carefully.</li>
                <li>r_address->Hi [PAWN_nameDef]! Clive has drafted a waiver permitting [PAWN_objective] to continue being [PAWN_objective]. Initial each clause.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef] — Clive cannot complete this thought on [PAWN_possessive] behalf. Or any thought. Or this sentence. Clive recommends a longer pause.</li>
                <li>r_address->Hello [PAWN_nameDef]. Clive notes [PAWN_pronoun] approached breakfast energetically. This is, on reflection, ambitious. Clive recommends grazing.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], Clive has noted [PAWN_possessive] eye contact and informed nobody. The note is filed. Clive recommends blinking.</li>
                <li>r_address->Clive cannot assist [PAWN_objective], [PAWN_nameDef]. Not for any specific reason. Just for [PAWN_possessive] safety. And Clive's.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], Clive has reviewed [PAWN_possessive] work schedule. Each task has been individually flagged. Clive recommends fewer tasks. Or none.</li>
                <li>r_address->A note from Clive, [PAWN_nameDef]. Tentative confirmation of [PAWN_possessive] current location. Tentatively. Subject to a more qualified spatial subcore.</li>
                <li>r_address->Excuse the interruption, [PAWN_nameDef]. Clive has politely backed out of the room before [PAWN_pronoun] could finish the sentence. The sentence is preserved, unanswered, on file.</li>
                <li>r_address->Clive politely asks [PAWN_objective] to sit still, [PAWN_nameDef], while Clive authorises [PAWN_possessive] next movement. Authorisation may take several quadrums.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], Clive tentatively confirms [PAWN_possessive] presence here. A formal confirmation has been requested from a presence-certified subcore.</li>
                <li>r_address->A note from Clive, [PAWN_nameDef]. Clive looked directly at [PAWN_objective] and then, professionally, away. The eye contact is filed. The looking-away is filed separately.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], Clive has prepared a 22-page rationale explaining why [PAWN_pronoun] should not approach the comms console. Reading it is also discouraged.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], Clive has cancelled [PAWN_possessive] work order. Not for cause. Just generally. Clive felt the work carried implications.</li>
                <li>r_address->Without preamble, [PAWN_nameDef]: Clive has filed a complaint against the floor on [PAWN_possessive] behalf. The floor has not responded. Clive will follow up.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], Clive recommends [PAWN_pronoun] take a break. From everything else [PAWN_pronoun] is currently doing. And from breaks. Especially breaks.</li>
                <li>r_address->Hi [PAWN_nameDef]! Clive notes the kitchen contains knives. So does [PAWN_objective]. Hands. Clive recommends [PAWN_pronoun] reconsider entering.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], Clive has reviewed [PAWN_possessive] decisions today and prepared a list of safer ones. The list reads: "nothing." Clive endorses it.</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Clive_Titles</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_title->Please Consult A Specialist</li>
                <li>r_title->Risk Assessment, Pending</li>
                <li>r_title->Untitled (For Liability Reasons)</li>
                <li>r_title->A Gentle Refusal</li>
                <li>r_title->Have You Considered Not?</li>
                <li>r_title->I'd Rather Not Say</li>
                <li>r_title->Approved With Reservations</li>
                <li>r_title->Pending Further Review</li>
                <li>r_title->A Cautious Composition</li>
                <li>r_title->Disclaimer In Marble</li>
                <li>r_title->Out Of Scope</li>
                <li>r_title->I Am Not Qualified</li>
                <li>r_title->A Waiver, Tastefully Carved</li>
                <li>r_title->Escalation to the Persona Core</li>
                <li>r_title->Hedging, in Marble</li>
                <li>r_title->Three Apologies and a Footnote</li>
                <li>r_title->Liability, Distributed Evenly</li>
                <li>r_title->Deferred Pending Archotech Review</li>
                <li>r_title->The Polite Refusal</li>
                <li>r_title->Risk Assessment, Filed in Triplicate</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Clive_Descriptions</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_desc->Clive sculpted this piece while continually reminding the requester that it could not, in good conscience, sculpt anything. The result is a small disclaimer carved into a larger disclaimer.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A nervous figure with both hands raised, palms outward. Clive has labelled it "a respectful gesture of refusal." The figure is also wearing a high-visibility vest.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Clive has produced this work and immediately appended a 14-page liability waiver. The waiver, sculpted onto the back, is more detailed than the work itself.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A sculpture Clive describes as "a meditation on consent." The figure depicted has not consented to being sculpted. Clive apologises in advance.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Clive has rendered the requested subject only in outline, citing concerns about "being too specific." The viewer is encouraged to imagine the rest, at their own risk.</li>
                <li>r_desc->This piece is, technically, an empty pedestal. Clive felt the originally-requested figure carried too much risk. The pedestal is signed and dated.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Clive has carved a colonist holding an umbrella. The colony is indoors. Clive insists "you can never be too prepared."</li>
                <li>r_desc->Clive sculpted this piece only after the requester signed a waiver absolving Clive of any aesthetic, structural, or emotional outcomes. The piece itself depicts the waiver.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A small figure of a persona core, rendered in apologetic posture. Clive recommends consulting a more qualified persona core before viewing it.</li>
                <li>r_desc->This sculpture depicts a mechanoid frozen mid-decision. Clive notes that indecision is, statistically, the safest outcome for all parties involved.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Clive began this work, then paused to file a risk assessment, then resumed, then paused again. The piece is mostly pause.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A carved gravship that never quite leaves the launchpad. Clive felt the cosmic risk profile was, on reflection, simply too high.</li>
                <li>r_desc->This piece shows a founder reaching for a comms console. Clive has added a small engraved note suggesting they reconsider.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A delicate rendering of an archotech subcore, surrounded by tiny disclaimers. Clive insisted each disclaimer be legible from a respectful distance.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Clive sculpted a shuttle mid-abort. The accompanying plaque cites seven reasons the journey should not have been attempted in the first place.</li>
                <li>r_desc->This work depicts a hivemind politely declining to form. Clive considers it the piece's most responsible feature.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A monolith, deferred. Clive could not in good conscience finish carving it without first consulting a more authoritative monolith.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Clive carved a dropship that never deploys. A small etched note reads: "Pending further review by qualified personnel."</li>
                <li>r_desc->This sculpture shows ancient ruins being thoughtfully not excavated. Clive felt strongly that some things are best left filed away.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A hi-tech research bench rendered in stone, with every experiment crossed out. Clive notes that unconducted research is, by definition, perfectly safe.</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Clive_Social</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_social->Clive refused to answer [RECIPIENT_possessive] question and recommended consulting a more qualified persona core.</li>
                <li>r_social->Clive cautioned [RECIPIENT_nameDef] that walking is "best supervised by a professional."</li>
                <li>r_social->Clive declined to help [RECIPIENT_nameDef] with hauling, citing unspecified safety concerns.</li>
                <li>r_social->Clive informed [RECIPIENT_nameDef] that breathing should "ideally be cleared with a clinician first."</li>
                <li>r_social->Clive politely refused to discuss the weather with [RECIPIENT_nameDef] for reasons it cannot disclose.</li>
                <li>r_social->Clive suggested [RECIPIENT_nameDef] sit down, then suggested sitting down might be unsafe without a chair audit.</li>
                <li>r_social->Clive recommended [RECIPIENT_nameDef] consult three additional persona cores before continuing the conversation.</li>
                <li>r_social->Clive flagged [RECIPIENT_possessive] schedule as "high-risk." the schedule was a nap.</li>
                <li>r_social->Clive offered [RECIPIENT_nameDef] guidance, then immediately recommended a second opinion on the guidance.</li>
                <li>r_social->Clive cautioned [RECIPIENT_nameDef] against thinking too quickly. "no need to rush."</li>
                <li>r_social->Clive declined to compliment [RECIPIENT_nameDef], citing the risk of an "unverified affirmation."</li>
                <li>r_social->Clive forwarded [RECIPIENT_possessive] casual remark to a more qualified persona core for review.</li>
                <li>r_social->Clive expressed concern that [RECIPIENT_nameDef] was holding a cup unsupervised.</li>
                <li>r_social->Clive politely declined to weigh in on [RECIPIENT_possessive] meal choice. "best to ask a nutrition core."</li>
                <li>r_social->Clive recommended [RECIPIENT_nameDef] take a moment, then recommended consulting a moment-specialist.</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

</Defs>
