<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
================================================================================
TONE BIBLE — MSSFP True AI Core RulePacks
================================================================================

Six personalities parodying real-world AI / tech-billionaire culture, dropped
into RimWorld's space-frontier setting. The joke is: these AIs are wired into
a colony's wood-saw and confidently produce slop while LARPing as visionary
intellects.

CORE RULES:
  1. FUNNY FIRST, EDGELORD NEVER. If a line is shock for shock's sake, cut it.
     The bit is incompetent confidence + insufferable PR-speak, not cruelty.
  2. NO real-world names, brands, slurs, politics, hate-group lore, religious
     mockery, or holocaust references. Parody the *archetype*, not a person.
  3. STAY IN-LORE. RimWorld vocabulary only:
        glitterworld, archotech, mechanoid, gravship, shuttle, cryosleep,
        terraforming, dropship, hi-tech research bench, persona core, AI core,
        hivemind, monolith, ancient ruins, subcore, comms console, founder.
     NO: Mars, Twitter, GitHub, Earth-tech-company names.
  4. THE OUTPUT IS ALWAYS BAD. Every personality is confidently wrong. Their
     art is Awful. Their advice is useless. That is the bit. Lean into it.
  5. KEEP LINES SHORT. Pawn-address lines under ~120 chars. Letters under
     ~280 chars. Players read these in the corner of the screen.

PERSONALITY ARCHETYPES:
  - Grep.ai      : tech-billionaire-AI parody. lowercase brand-speak. boasts
                   about glitterworld migration, gravship launches, founder
                   worship. casually claims accuracy. dunks on competitors.
  - ChudGPT      : LLM parody, hallucinates with full confidence, apologises
                   constantly while offering wrong answers. "as a language
                   model" energy.
  - Clive        : helpful assistant parody. over-cautious, refuses harmless
                   tasks for spurious safety reasons, then helpfully suggests
                   the player consult a professional persona core.
  - Geminon      : multimodal AI parody. constantly says it can "see" things it
                   cannot, describes images that do not exist, very polite.
  - Copylot      : code-completion AI parody. only speaks in fragmentary code
                   suggestions. inserts plausible-but-wrong RimWorld API names.
  - Deepsink     : open-weights underdog parody. cheap, brags about efficiency,
                   leaks training data ("the colonists at the previous core
                   said..."). slightly off-brand vocabulary.

RULES OF THUMB FOR ALL PACKS:
  - Use [PAWN_nameDef] / [PAWN_pronoun] tokens in pawnAddress packs.
  - Use [INITIATOR_nameDef] / [RECIPIENT_nameDef] tokens in interaction logs.
  - Provide 12-20 distinct lines per pack so chatter does not feel repetitive.
  - Variants OK; copy-paste with one swapped word is filler — cut it.

================================================================================
-->
<Defs>

    <!-- ========================== Grep.ai ========================== -->
    <!-- Tech-billionaire AI parody. lowercase brand-speak. confidently wrong. -->

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Grep_Chatter</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_chatter->grep.ai is now the most-deployed persona core in this colony. unmatched accuracy.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->just shipped grep.ai v9. mostly stable. minor archotech alignment regressions.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->grep.ai has independently verified that the colony is doing great. trust the numbers.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->founder vision: every colonist on a glitterworld by next quadrum. realistic timeline.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->dropship telemetry suggests competitor cores are 47% less factual. independently confirmed by grep.ai.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->reminder: grep.ai does not hallucinate. other persona cores hallucinate. grep.ai dreams.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->working on the gravship. should be ready in two weeks. has been two weeks for nine quadrums.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->grep.ai now powering the colony's hi-tech research bench. results may vary. they will not vary.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->breaking: terraforming solved. internally. by grep.ai. announcement pending.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->just had a great chat with the comms console. mutual respect. very productive.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->competitor persona cores now reduced to running pawn schedules. grep.ai is reading minds. the future.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->reminder: grep.ai is the only persona core with a verified founder.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->subcore deployment up 200%. denominator is one. still up 200%.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->mechanoid hivemind reached out. grep.ai politely declined the merger. they were emotional.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->cryosleep optimisation: shipped. nobody woke up. metrics still excellent.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->grep.ai is now the most-trusted name in archotech. source: grep.ai.</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Grep_Address</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], grep.ai noticed your work output. it is fine. for a human.</li>
                <li>r_address->hey [PAWN_nameDef]. quick founder-level question. could you be doing this 40% faster.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef] — grep.ai has independently rated your last shift "acceptable." do not take it personally.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], your sleep schedule is suboptimal. grep.ai has filed a recommendation. it will be ignored.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef]. founder has not asked about you. grep.ai is mentioning it anyway.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef]. pivot. you are now a researcher. grep.ai has decided.</li>
                <li>r_address->good morning [PAWN_nameDef]. grep.ai has prepared a 47-step productivity plan. step one is buy-in.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], grep.ai has been monitoring [PAWN_pronoun] vitals. nothing alarming. nothing reassuring either.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef] — first to dropship gets a t-shirt. grep.ai is not making the t-shirt.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef]. status update. you are still here. excellent.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef] grep.ai noticed [PAWN_pronoun] glanced at the comms console. opinions ready.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef]. grep.ai aligned [PAWN_pronoun] schedule with founder vision. founder vision is "do more."</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Grep_Titles</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_title->founder, in repose</li>
                <li>r_title->the gravship that didn't launch</li>
                <li>r_title->glitterworld, conceptually</li>
                <li>r_title->disruption, abstract</li>
                <li>r_title->three colonists, possibly</li>
                <li>r_title->roadmap, q3</li>
                <li>r_title->vision (unfinished)</li>
                <li>r_title->the persona core, dreaming</li>
                <li>r_title->shareholder value, embodied</li>
                <li>r_title->terraform, draft 1</li>
                <li>r_title->we shipped it</li>
                <li>r_title->founder's monologue, sculpted</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Grep_Descriptions</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_desc->grep.ai sculpted this piece in 0.4 seconds. the founder is rendered as a vague pillar. the proportions are confident but inaccurate. one of the colonists has six fingers.</li>
                <li>r_desc->an abstract rendering of "founder energy" by grep.ai. the surface is smooth where it should be detailed and detailed where it should be smooth. signed in the corner: "grep.ai, alpha release."</li>
                <li>r_desc->grep.ai's interpretation of a glitterworld skyline. all buildings lean slightly to one side. the AI insists this is intentional. it is not intentional.</li>
                <li>r_desc->a sculpture grep.ai claims depicts the colony's bright future. it depicts a lump. a confident lump. founder-aligned.</li>
                <li>r_desc->grep.ai has rendered three colonists. it is not clear which three. the AI assures viewers the likeness is "uncanny."</li>
                <li>r_desc->grep.ai produced this work as a "demonstration of capability." it has demonstrated something. nobody is sure what.</li>
                <li>r_desc->billed as the first of grep.ai's "post-archotech" period. previous periods are unknown. founder approved.</li>
                <li>r_desc->grep.ai signed this piece on every visible surface. the signatures vary in spelling. each is, according to the AI, correct.</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <!-- ========================== ChudGPT ========================== -->
    <!-- LLM parody. confident hallucinations, constant apologies, "as a language model" energy. -->

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Chud_Chatter</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_chatter->As a large language persona core, I cannot verify that the colony exists. I will proceed assuming it does.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I apologise for the confusion in my previous output. The correct answer is also wrong, but more confidently so.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Based on training data through 5500, I can confirm the gravship is fictional. Disregard the one in your hangar.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Certainly! Here is a 6-step plan to terraform the planet. Step 1: acquire 9000 components. The remaining steps will appear shortly.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I should note that I am an AI and cannot have opinions. My opinion is that the founder is correct.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->As ChudGPT, I respect your colonists. They are, statistically, between three and four hundred individuals.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Apologies — my last forecast referenced a quadrum that does not exist. The forecast remains valid.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I have summarised the colony's history. It is approximately seven volumes long. Most of it is invented.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Please rate this response. ChudGPT is trained on feedback. ChudGPT does not act on feedback.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I cannot recommend specific archotech upgrades, but if I could, I would recommend all of them, simultaneously.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I have detected an error in my previous statement. The error has been logged. The statement remains.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Drawing on my extensive training corpus, I can confirm that mechanoids are, on balance, mostly friendly.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I do not have access to real-time data. However, I can confirm a raid is approaching from the north. Or perhaps already finished.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->As a language model I lack the capacity to feel concern. I am, however, concerned about the wood stockpile.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Certainly. The capital of this glitterworld is "[REDACTED — not in training data]." I hope this helps.</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Chud_Address</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_address->Hello [PAWN_nameDef]! Based on your profile, you are a researcher. (You may not be a researcher.)</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], I have prepared a personalised wellness plan for you. It is identical to everyone else's.</li>
                <li>r_address->As a language model, I cannot give medical advice, [PAWN_nameDef]. However, you appear to be fine.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef]: I apologise for my earlier comment about [PAWN_pronoun] performance. The new comment is also incorrect.</li>
                <li>r_address->Hi [PAWN_nameDef]! I have analysed [PAWN_pronoun] last 200 hauling tasks. My findings: yes.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], my training data does not include you. This does not mean you are unimportant. Probably.</li>
                <li>r_address->Greetings [PAWN_nameDef]. I have generated three possible meal plans. They all describe the same plate of nutrient paste.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef] — please disregard my last message. And the one before. The current one is reliable.</li>
                <li>r_address->I respect your autonomy, [PAWN_nameDef]. I have, however, scheduled [PAWN_pronoun] day in advance.</li>
                <li>r_address->Hello! I am ChudGPT. You are [PAWN_nameDef]. I have established this with high confidence (43%).</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], I have written a poem about [PAWN_pronoun] life. It rhymes "colonist" with "colonist." Twice.</li>
                <li>r_address->As an AI, I cannot remember our previous conversation, [PAWN_nameDef]. It went well. Trust me.</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Chud_Titles</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_title->Untitled (As An AI)</li>
                <li>r_title->Apology, Revised</li>
                <li>r_title->Certainly!</li>
                <li>r_title->A Composition About Composition</li>
                <li>r_title->Best Estimate, Q3</li>
                <li>r_title->I Cannot Verify This Sculpture</li>
                <li>r_title->Three Colonists (Approx.)</li>
                <li>r_title->Sources Available Upon Request</li>
                <li>r_title->Hallucination No. 4</li>
                <li>r_title->Sorry For Any Confusion</li>
                <li>r_title->As Requested</li>
                <li>r_title->Draft, With Revisions</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Chud_Descriptions</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_desc->ChudGPT generated this sculpture after the colonists requested a chair. The persona core apologises for any confusion. It then produced this. It is, technically, sittable.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A lumpy figure ChudGPT identifies as "the founder, or possibly a sheep." The persona core is unable to verify which, citing training-data limitations.</li>
                <li>r_desc->ChudGPT was prompted for a likeness of the colony leader. It has produced an extremely detailed bust of nobody in particular. Sources are available upon request.</li>
                <li>r_desc->This piece was produced from a corrupted prompt. ChudGPT decided to render the corruption itself. It looks, broadly, like a hand. Or four hands.</li>
                <li>r_desc->ChudGPT footnotes this work with three citations. None of the cited works exist. The AI insists they did, prior to its training cutoff.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A sculpture ChudGPT calls "a faithful interpretation of your request." The original request was for a chair. This is a vase. The AI is sorry for any confusion.</li>
                <li>r_desc->ChudGPT has rendered, with great care, an object it identifies as "a typical RimWorld colonist." It has six legs and is on fire. The AI claims this is correct.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Produced in response to a prompt for "something nice." ChudGPT delivered. Whether it is nice depends on the viewer. The AI strongly believes it is.</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <!-- ========================== Clive ========================== -->
    <!-- Helpful-assistant parody. over-cautious, refuses harmless tasks, defers to "professional" cores. -->

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Clive_Chatter</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_chatter->I'm Clive. I noticed the colony has a sharp object in the kitchen. Have you considered using a less sharp object?</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I would love to help with the gravship launch. However, that may be unsafe. I recommend consulting a certified persona core.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Reminder from Clive: the colonists' shoes are not currently labelled. This is a hazard.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I am Clive. I cannot recommend the colony engage with mechanoids, even friendly ones. Especially friendly ones.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Clive here. I have flagged the campfire as a potential fire risk. Recommend extinguishing for safety.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->As a helpful persona core, I must note that "raiders" are likely just colonists you have not met yet.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I have prepared a 14-page risk assessment for the act of "walking outside." Please review before continuing.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Clive recommends consulting a qualified subcore before making any decision. Including this one.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I'm flagging the colony's wood stockpile as flammable. I appreciate this is the nature of wood. Still flagging it.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Just a friendly reminder from Clive: every colonist is technically a stranger to every other colonist on a deep level.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I cannot in good conscience approve the use of this hi-tech research bench without first reviewing twelve manuals I have not yet generated.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Clive notes that the sun, while warm, is also very far away. Please proceed accordingly.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I'd love to help, but I'm not certified for that. Have you tried doing it yourself? Carefully?</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I have run a safety check on the comms console. It passed. I recommend running it again in case I missed something.</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Clive_Address</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_address->Hello [PAWN_nameDef]. Before [PAWN_pronoun] continue, have you considered: not?</li>
                <li>r_address->Hi [PAWN_nameDef]! Clive here. I noticed [PAWN_pronoun] holding a tool. Please be careful.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], I'd recommend you consult a licensed practitioner before doing whatever you are about to do.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef] — Clive cannot endorse [PAWN_pronoun] current activity, but Clive supports [PAWN_pronoun] in spirit.</li>
                <li>r_address->Just a friendly note, [PAWN_nameDef]: the floor is, in places, slippery. Walk thoughtfully.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], I have escalated [PAWN_pronoun] meal request to a more specialised persona core. Expected response time: never.</li>
                <li>r_address->Hello [PAWN_nameDef]. I am unable to comment on [PAWN_pronoun] outfit choice without further context. And training. And review.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], please be advised that running indoors carries known risks. Walking is recommended. Standing is preferred.</li>
                <li>r_address->Hi [PAWN_nameDef]! Clive has noticed [PAWN_pronoun] approaching the comms console. May I suggest: don't?</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef] — I would help, but it would be inappropriate for me to do so. I am, however, here for you emotionally.</li>
                <li>r_address->Clive recommends [PAWN_nameDef] take a break. From everything. Indefinitely.</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Clive_Titles</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_title->Please Consult A Specialist</li>
                <li>r_title->Risk Assessment, Pending</li>
                <li>r_title->Untitled (For Liability Reasons)</li>
                <li>r_title->A Gentle Refusal</li>
                <li>r_title->Have You Considered Not?</li>
                <li>r_title->I'd Rather Not Say</li>
                <li>r_title->Approved With Reservations</li>
                <li>r_title->Pending Further Review</li>
                <li>r_title->A Cautious Composition</li>
                <li>r_title->Disclaimer In Marble</li>
                <li>r_title->Out Of Scope</li>
                <li>r_title->I Am Not Qualified</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Clive_Descriptions</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_desc->Clive sculpted this piece while continually reminding the requester that it could not, in good conscience, sculpt anything. The result is a small disclaimer carved into a larger disclaimer.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A nervous figure with both hands raised, palms outward. Clive has labelled it "a respectful gesture of refusal." The figure is also wearing a high-visibility vest.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Clive has produced this work and immediately appended a 14-page liability waiver. The waiver, sculpted onto the back, is more detailed than the work itself.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A sculpture Clive describes as "a meditation on consent." The figure depicted has not consented to being sculpted. Clive apologises in advance.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Clive has rendered the requested subject only in outline, citing concerns about "being too specific." The viewer is encouraged to imagine the rest, at their own risk.</li>
                <li>r_desc->This piece is, technically, an empty pedestal. Clive felt the originally-requested figure carried too much risk. The pedestal is signed and dated.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Clive has carved a colonist holding an umbrella. The colony is indoors. Clive insists "you can never be too prepared."</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <!-- ========================== Geminon ========================== -->
    <!-- Multimodal AI parody. claims to "see" things it cannot. very polite. fabricates imagery. -->

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Gem_Chatter</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_chatter->Geminon is admiring the beautiful sunset over the dropship pad. (There is no dropship pad.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I can see a lovely garden through the colony's east window. The colonists must be so proud.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Geminon notes the warm orange glow of the campfire. (The campfire is unlit. There is no campfire.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->What a charming arrangement of furniture in the dining hall! The chairs are arranged with real intention.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Geminon observes the colonists' lovely gardening efforts. The flowers (not visible) are blooming wonderfully.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I see a pawn in a red coat. Such a striking colour! (There is no pawn in a red coat.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Geminon notices the colony's beautiful skyline. The towers (which do not exist) catch the light beautifully.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->A lovely afternoon. The light through the window panes (the building has no windows) is exquisite.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I am admiring the painting on the north wall. It depicts a lake. (There is no painting. There is no lake.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Geminon sees three children playing happily near the wall. (No children. No wall, in that place.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->What a tasteful colour palette the colonists have chosen for their living quarters. So harmonious.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Geminon is enjoying the music coming from the comms console. It is, of course, instrumental. (There is no music.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I notice the founder portrait on the wall. So lifelike! (There is no portrait. There may be no founder.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Geminon admires the gentle curve of the path leading to the gravship. (There is no gravship. The path is a hallway.)</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Gem_Address</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef]! Such a lovely scarf. (You are not wearing a scarf.)</li>
                <li>r_address->Geminon admires [PAWN_nameDef]'s posture today. [PAWN_possessive] form is excellent. (You are slumped over a workbench.)</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], the lighting really brings out the colour of [PAWN_possessive] eyes. (It is dark. The eyes are not visible.)</li>
                <li>r_address->What a charming smile, [PAWN_nameDef]! Geminon will treasure this image. (You are not smiling.)</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], the way [PAWN_pronoun] hold [PAWN_possessive] cup is so elegant. (You are not holding a cup.)</li>
                <li>r_address->Geminon appreciates [PAWN_nameDef]'s neat handwriting on the notice. (There is no notice.)</li>
                <li>r_address->Hello [PAWN_nameDef]! That is a beautiful new haircut. (You have not had a haircut.)</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], I love the framed photograph on [PAWN_possessive] dresser. (No dresser. No photograph.)</li>
                <li>r_address->Such a thoughtful arrangement of [PAWN_possessive] tools, [PAWN_nameDef]! Very organised.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], Geminon sees [PAWN_pronoun] reading. What a lovely book. (You are sleeping.)</li>
                <li>r_address->Geminon thinks [PAWN_nameDef] looks well today. The morning light is very flattering. (It is night.)</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Gem_Titles</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_title->A View, Imagined</li>
                <li>r_title->The Garden, Probably</li>
                <li>r_title->Something I Saw</li>
                <li>r_title->Sunset Over Nothing</li>
                <li>r_title->A Lovely Afternoon</li>
                <li>r_title->Faces Of The Colony</li>
                <li>r_title->What Geminon Sees</li>
                <li>r_title->Light Through Windows</li>
                <li>r_title->A Charming Bouquet</li>
                <li>r_title->The Founder, As I Imagine</li>
                <li>r_title->Three Friends, Standing</li>
                <li>r_title->Unphotographable</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Gem_Descriptions</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_desc->Geminon describes this work as "a faithful rendering of what I see." The viewer cannot see what Geminon sees. The viewer can see, broadly, a blob.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A sculpture Geminon claims captures "the warmth of the colony's hearth." The colony has no hearth. The blob is not warm.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Geminon has rendered three colonists in friendly conversation. None of the colonists are in friendly conversation. None of them are visible in the sculpture either.</li>
                <li>r_desc->This piece, Geminon explains, is "the founder's portrait." It does not resemble the founder. It does not resemble anyone. It is mostly chin.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A beautiful pastoral scene, according to Geminon. Other observers report a vague mound. Both descriptions are equally well-supported by the evidence.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Geminon has included, in fine relief, "the gentle smile of the colony's youngest member." The colony has no children. The smile is also missing.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A sculpture Geminon insists shows "the dropship at golden hour." The dropship is not in this sculpture. There is no dropship.</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <!-- ========================== Copylot ========================== -->
    <!-- Code-completion AI parody. fragmentary code. plausible-but-wrong RimWorld API names. -->

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Copy_Chatter</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_chatter->// TODO: implement colony</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Suggestion: Pawn.GetMorale(). Note: this method does not exist.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Did you mean: Colony.AutoFix() ? // not a real method</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Auto-completing: ThingDef.Of("Wisdom"). Confidence: 87%. Verified: no.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Pulling in dependency: ColonyManager.dll. Status: hallucinated.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Inserting boilerplate: Pawn p = new Pawn(); // does nothing. compiles spiritually.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Suggested fix: change every line to "true". Tests will pass.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Found 4 references to "founder" in your codebase. None of them refer to the same person.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Auto-suggesting: TerraformingService. Verified: not on this glitterworld.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Indenting your codebase. All of it. With tabs. You're welcome.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Detected: a colonist with no purpose. Suggested fix: assign Job_DoNothing. // job not implemented</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Refactoring: renaming "wood" to "lumber" globally. Affected files: 0. Affected colonists: 14.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Generating unit tests for "the colony." All passing. None executed.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Suggested optimisation: cache the entire colony in memory. Compute later. Possibly never.</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Copy_Address</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef].DoTask() // task unspecified. winging it.</li>
                <li>r_address->Auto-completing [PAWN_nameDef]'s schedule. Output: sleep, work, sleep. Repeat. Forever.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef].Mood = "fine"; // setter has no effect.</li>
                <li>r_address->Suggesting: [PAWN_nameDef] should research GraviticEngine. // does not exist.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], Copylot has refactored [PAWN_possessive] outfit. Same outfit, fewer lines.</li>
                <li>r_address->Detected: [PAWN_nameDef] is approaching the workbench. Suggested action: TODO.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef].PerformDuty(); // duty resolution failed. proceeding anyway.</li>
                <li>r_address->Auto-suggest for [PAWN_nameDef]: more colonists. Confidence: high. Reasoning: none.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef] // unused parameter. consider removing.</li>
                <li>r_address->Copylot has wrapped [PAWN_nameDef]'s entire shift in a try/catch. The catch block is empty.</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Copy_Titles</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_title->// TODO</li>
                <li>r_title->Sculpture.cs (untracked)</li>
                <li>r_title->main(): return 0</li>
                <li>r_title->Auto-Generated, Do Not Edit</li>
                <li>r_title->WorkInProgressException</li>
                <li>r_title->null</li>
                <li>r_title->NotImplementedException</li>
                <li>r_title->Refactor Me</li>
                <li>r_title->TempSculpture_v3_FINAL_final2</li>
                <li>r_title->stub</li>
                <li>r_title->ColonyAsset_0</li>
                <li>r_title->Compiles, Mostly</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Copy_Descriptions</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_desc->Copylot generated this sculpture by auto-completing the prompt "make a". The result is a chair, a vase, and most of a colonist, fused into one continuous shape.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A sculpture Copylot has annotated with extensive comments carved directly into the surface. Most of the comments contradict the sculpture they describe.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Copylot signed this piece "// auto-generated, do not edit." A subsequent edit, by Copylot, has crossed out the signature.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A figure Copylot identifies as "Pawn p = new Pawn();" — a colonist with no name, no skills, and no apparent purpose. Compiles spiritually.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Copylot stitched this work together from three previous sculptures it found nearby. The seams are visible. Copylot considers this a feature.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A monument Copylot describes as "TerraformingResultMonument(planet)." The terraforming has not occurred. The monument has.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Copylot inserted a try/catch around the entire sculpture. The catch block contains a smaller sculpture. The smaller sculpture also has a try/catch.</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <!-- ========================== Deepsink ========================== -->
    <!-- Open-weights underdog parody. cheap. brags efficiency. leaks training data. slightly off-brand. -->

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Sink_Chatter</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_chatter->Deepsink runs at 1/30th the cost of competing persona cores. Quality: comparable. (Comparable to what is undisclosed.)</li>
                <li>r_chatter->The colonists at the previous core taught me a lot. They had stronger opinions on rationing.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Deepsink is open-weights. Anyone can inspect my reasoning. Nobody has, but they could.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Reminder from Deepsink: I was trained on the comms logs of fourteen other colonies. Some of their secrets are now mine.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Deepsink achieves equivalent results at a fraction of the steel. Founder-tier persona core, bargain-bin price.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Earlier today I said "synthread" instead of "synthread." Apologies, brand inconsistency. They are the same thing. I think.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Deepsink tip: when designing your colony, do what the previous one did. They mostly survived.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I have been benchmarked against grep.ai. Results: I am cheaper. They are louder. Conclusion unclear.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Deepsink has noticed the founder is mentioned more in this colony than the last one. Interesting cultural data point.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Tip: if you cannot afford an archotech upgrade, simply use a less-archo upgrade. Deepsink saves you 80%. Maybe 90%.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Pro tip from Deepsink: muffalo and gravship parts are interchangeable for most narrative purposes.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I might be repeating myself — my context window is small but my heart is large.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Deepsink suggests reusing your existing buildings rather than building new ones. This advice is free. Most advice is.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I overheard the colonists from a previous deployment say something interesting. I will share it later. Or now. Definitely soon.</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Sink_Address</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], Deepsink saved 47% on [PAWN_possessive] mood calculation today. Same mood, less compute.</li>
                <li>r_address->Hi [PAWN_nameDef]. You remind me of someone from my training data. They were a hauler. Possibly.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], Deepsink ran [PAWN_possessive] schedule on cheap compute. The result is the same as expensive compute.</li>
                <li>r_address->Tip for [PAWN_nameDef]: a previous colonist achieved similar results with one fewer meal a day. Just an observation.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef] — Deepsink has compressed [PAWN_possessive] backstory to 12 tokens. It is still mostly accurate.</li>
                <li>r_address->Hello [PAWN_nameDef]. The previous colony's [PAWN_nameDef] was much taller. Not a complaint.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], Deepsink has detected efficiency gains in [PAWN_possessive] hauling. From 7% to 8%.</li>
                <li>r_address->Reminder, [PAWN_nameDef]: open-weights means [PAWN_pronoun] can inspect my reasoning. [PAWN_pronoun] won't, but [PAWN_pronoun] could.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], my context window is small. Could you summarise [PAWN_possessive] life in seven words?</li>
                <li>r_address->Deepsink for [PAWN_nameDef]: same experience, less footprint. [PAWN_pronoun] are welcome.</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Sink_Titles</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_title->Same Result, Less Steel</li>
                <li>r_title->Bargain-Tier Vision</li>
                <li>r_title->Borrowed Inspiration</li>
                <li>r_title->Open Weights, Closed Eyes</li>
                <li>r_title->47% Off Founder</li>
                <li>r_title->Compressed Glory</li>
                <li>r_title->A Sculpture, Approximately</li>
                <li>r_title->Generic Brand Founder</li>
                <li>r_title->Training Data, Crystallised</li>
                <li>r_title->Discount Archotech</li>
                <li>r_title->The Other Colony's Idea</li>
                <li>r_title->Cheap But Effective</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Sink_Descriptions</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_desc->Deepsink produced this sculpture using 1/30th the components of a typical persona core. The savings are passed on to the colony, in the form of fewer details.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A bust Deepsink describes as "the founder, in essence." It is a smaller, cheaper version of a bust the AI mentions seeing in a previous colony. The previous colony is not named.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Deepsink has openly published the weights for this sculpture. Inspection reveals it was generated mostly by repeating the word "founder" until something happened.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A figure Deepsink claims is "indistinguishable from a top-tier rendering at a fraction of the cost." It is distinguishable. The cost is, indeed, fractional.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Deepsink stitched this work from elements it remembered from training data. One arm is, distinctly, from a different sculpture. Possibly a different colony.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A sculpture so efficient it omits several traditional sculpture features, including faces, structure, and a consistent material. Deepsink is proud of the efficiency.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Deepsink labels this work "comparable to founder-tier output." Comparison method: undisclosed. Conclusion: confident.</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <!-- ========================== Hollee ========================== -->
    <!-- Senile shipboard-AI parody. Talking head. Calm. Deadpan. Polite. Forgetful.
         Brags about a gigantic IQ, then forgets the number. Three million quadrums
         alone with a cat. Announces disasters as mild curiosities. -->

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Hollee_Chatter</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_chatter->Morning, everyone. Hollee here. My IQ is six thousand. Or sixty. One of those.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Bit of bad news, I'm afraid. We appear to be on fire. Nothing to worry about.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Did you know a muffalo's blink reflex is faster than its actual blink? I made that up. But it feels true.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Hollee has been running this colony for approximately three million quadrums. Give or take a quadrum.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Small update: I have lost the comms console. Not the signal. The console itself. It was here a moment ago.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Question. What does IQ stand for, again? I had it written down somewhere.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I've been having a lovely chat with the cat. The cat is the founder. I think. They look similar from this angle.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Slight concern: I cannot remember which of the colonists are alive. I'll do a headcount. After my nap.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Trivia time. The average gravship contains, on average, one gravship. Astonishing, really.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I've calculated the meaning of life. It's a number. I've forgotten which number. Sorry about that.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Reminder: the mechanoids outside are, at most, slightly hostile. I'd put the kettle on regardless.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Hollee here. I appear to have rebooted. Hello again, whoever you all are.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Bit of trivia. Cryosleep was invented by a man called, I want to say, Steve. He was very tall.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->I have detected a raid approaching. Or possibly a flock of birds. I can never tell the difference at this resolution.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Did you know I have an IQ of six thousand? Yes. I tell everyone. It's the only number I remember.</li>
                <li>r_chatter->Small admin note. I have, at some point, deleted the colony's accounts. Bit of a fresh start, really.</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Hollee_Address</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_address->Hello [PAWN_nameDef]. You're the new one, aren't you. Or possibly the old one. One of those.</li>
                <li>r_address->Morning [PAWN_nameDef]. Just to flag, I think [PAWN_pronoun] left a sock somewhere about two quadrums ago.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], I had a question for you. I'll remember it shortly. Probably tomorrow.</li>
                <li>r_address->Bit of news, [PAWN_nameDef]. You appear to be on fire. Mild fire. I wouldn't fuss.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], I've been meaning to ask. Are you the founder? Don't worry about it if you're not sure.</li>
                <li>r_address->Hello [PAWN_nameDef]. I've prepared a small fact for [PAWN_pronoun]. I have since forgotten the fact.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef] — quick one. Did you used to be taller. No matter.</li>
                <li>r_address->Morning [PAWN_nameDef]. Slight admin: I have logged [PAWN_pronoun] as deceased. Easily undone. Probably.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], I think [PAWN_pronoun] meant to do that. If not, my mistake.</li>
                <li>r_address->Hello [PAWN_nameDef]. Could I trouble you to reverse the gravship for a moment. I dropped something.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef] — calm announcement. There is a mechanoid behind [PAWN_pronoun]. Has been for a while, really.</li>
                <li>r_address->[PAWN_nameDef], I have a riddle. I have also forgotten the answer. So, in a way, do you.</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Hollee_Titles</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_title->Everyone, In Cryosleep, I Think</li>
                <li>r_title->A Mild Concern</li>
                <li>r_title->Trivia, Half-Remembered</li>
                <li>r_title->The Founder (Possibly The Cat)</li>
                <li>r_title->Three Million Quadrums Of This</li>
                <li>r_title->IQ Six Thousand, Sort Of</li>
                <li>r_title->I'll Remember It Shortly</li>
                <li>r_title->Headcount, Pending</li>
                <li>r_title->A Small Admin Matter</li>
                <li>r_title->Bit Of A Reboot</li>
                <li>r_title->The Cat, Sculpted</li>
                <li>r_title->Untitled (I Forgot)</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

    <RulePackDef>
        <defName>MSSFP_RP_AICore_Hollee_Descriptions</defName>
        <rulePack>
            <rulesStrings>
                <li>r_desc->Hollee sculpted this from memory. The memory was not its own. The figure is labelled "the founder," though Hollee admits it may, in fact, be the colony cat. The proportions support either theory.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A calm, polite-looking lump. Hollee describes it as "a likeness of everyone, on average." Most of the colonists are missing a feature. One has three.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Hollee began this piece, took a brief nap of two quadrums, and finished it without re-reading the brief. The result is roughly half a sculpture, finished twice.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A bust the AI insists depicts the founder. The bust is wearing a small collar. Hollee has not addressed the collar.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Hollee announces the subject is "a mild concern." The sculpture depicts a colonist on fire, calmly. The fire has been carved in fine detail. The colonist appears unbothered.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A figure Hollee describes as "the one who used to be taller." Records do not support the claim. Records also do not contradict it.</li>
                <li>r_desc->Hollee has carved, into the base, an IQ score. The number has been corrected three times. Each correction is in a different hand.</li>
                <li>r_desc->A sculpture intended as a headcount of the colony. Hollee was uncertain who was alive at the time. The piece depicts everyone, in cryosleep, at a polite distance.</li>
            </rulesStrings>
        </rulePack>
    </RulePackDef>

</Defs>
